The end of the line is here!
End of Line
This circle has the cutest vendors!
And the art is gorgeous...
Must be an original story.
Sakura, we ran out of change!
Seriously?!
Wow, your booth is packed!
May? Cecil?
What are you doing here?
I came because May said that
this world has its own festival.
Lord Hinata... what are you wearing?
U-Uh, this is...
Excuse me! One comic, please.
Give me just a moment!
I didn't expect this many people...
Miss Cecil, May...
Sorry, but we need your help!
Limit one new comic per customer, please!
We brought more change.
Thank you so much!
Today, I'm here hanging out with
my friend's doujin circle!
May, you can stream later. Help us!
End of Line
New Comic: Sold Out
We did it!
I can't believe we actually sold all of them!
Whew, that was hard work!
All you did was wave a camera
around in our faces.
By the way, is this a festival?
Well... for people like me,
it's the biggest festival of them all.
It's completely sold out...
Good job. You had fun, right?
Yes! Very much so!
Ooh, so your costumes were
modeled after these characters.
Yup! Sakura made them for us.
Did you forget that you tore it earlier?
Cosplaying's got its challenges.
Is this...?
Excuse me.
Could I speak with Miss Sakura?
Y-Yes, that's me.
Hello there. My name is Ando,
and I'm an editor for Takeshobo.
If you don't mind me asking,
are you interested in writing for
a professional publication?
Huh?
Whaaaaat?!
Takeshobo Co., Ltd.
Ando
I'll reach out to you again at a later date.
Take care.
G-Goodbye...
That's amazing, Mochida!
You caught the attention of a publisher!
Gonna be a professional mangaka?
Let's not get carried away!
But... it's a nice confidence boost.
I feel like I can do anything now!
Anything?
Then let's take some pictures in the plaza!
Huh?
Might as well since you're all dressed up.
Bell and Hinata, too!
You want us?
Yeah! The more the merrier!
Was this her plan from the beginning...?
Taking breaks is important, right?
Cecil, you perform emergency
surgery on Bell's costume!
Sakura and I will dismantle the booth!
When we're done, we'll meet in the plaza!
I swear... When May gets like that,
there's no stopping her.
Can you fix it?
As long as I've got a needle and thread.
For Pete's sake...
I'd prefer that you avoid doing anything
to draw attention to yourselves in public.
I've been tasked with bringing you
back home should something go wrong.
I wish you'd consider things
from my point of view.
I don't want to drag you back
if I can help it.
Which is why, Mariabell,
I urge you to cooperate—
Lord Hinata?
Mariabell?
B-Bell...
We're alone at last, Hinata-chan.
You're so adorable...
Are you really coming with me?
Which bathroom will you use?
Should your big sister
lend you a helping hand?
Quit it. People are staring at—
Wait, what...?
I used my magic to make us invisible.
To anyone without mana, it looks
as though nobody's standing here.
So, Hinata-chan...
B-Bell...
I'm only disguising our physical presence.
If you raise your voice or someone
touches you, we'll get caught.
So be good, okay?
Don't—
Oh?
Well, what do we have here?!
Hinata-chan, where did these come from?!
M-Mochida gave them to me...
And you actually wore them?!
Oh, Hinata-chan. How kinky.
Are you wearing a bra, too?
Good job, Sakura!
I don't mind batting for the other team
if it's with Hinata!
Wait, which team?!
Hey—!
Look at your teeny-tiny boobies!
I don't have boobs!
Only girls do, and I'm not—
Shh.
We'll get caught if you're too loud, remember?
Oh no, all your squirming
made the safety pin come off!
Naughty thing.
B-But... it wasn't my fault...
So cute!
N-Not in public...
You're going to drive me crazy...
That's just fine by me.
I'll embrace any and every part of you.
Your kinky side belongs solely to me...
Sh-She's intense...
Oh? Do I spy something beginning to
poke through your panties?
We can't do this, Bell...
Of course we can!
It doesn't matter that we're both girls.
Love conquers all, right?
Nope, not quite!
Put on some clothes!
Tsk.
I almost had him...
Not five seconds after I told you
to quit bothering Lord Hinata.
What's the matter with you?!
Sorry we're late!
Looks like we're all here.
Let's get started!
Excuse me! May I take a photo?
It's May from MayMay's Parallel Universe!
You were the vendors at that one booth, right?
Can I get a picture, too?
Alright, one at a time, please!
Nice job out there.
Photoshoots are hard work.
Yeah...
May's in a good mood.
Seems like it.
She must be used to this kind of thing.
Bell looks great. I think she
could be a popular cosplayer!
Uh-huh, probably...
I'm alone with Sunohara!
Um, Sunohara?
What's the matter?
It's just, that guy...
He keeps moving behind Bell...
Does he have a hidden camera?!
This is bad!
We should alert a staff member—
Excuse me.
C-Can't move...!
Would you mind coming with me for a minute?
What?
What's your problem, bitch?! Let go of—
I'm a guy.
WHAAAT?!
Sunohara...?
I-I'm sorry!
Everyone was having a good time,
and I brought down the mood...
No, you did nothing wrong.
But I was a little surprised.
Huh?
That's the first time I've ever seen
you get angry, Sunohara.
When I thought about a stranger
recording Bell without her consent,
I just started moving on autopilot...
Oh...
Hinata!
Thank you for saving me!
I've become so desensitized to people
giving me strange looks all the time.
You really are my hero, Hinata!
A hero...
We took so many pictures.
I can't wait to edit them!
Man, I'm starving...
Should we eat something on the way home?
Hey, Sunohara?
Huh?
Earlier, when you rescued Bell
from that creep...
It definitely caught me off guard,
and I was a little unnerved, but...
...you were really, really cool!
Y-Y'think so?
Bell might think of you as a hero, but...
I want you to know...
you're a hero in my mind, too!
Th-Thanks.
That's a weight off my shoulders!
Hinata! Sakura! What are you guys doing?
C'mon, let's get going!
Bell's waiting for us.
Something happen?
Nah, nothing too important.
Aren't friends supposed to
tell each other things?
Really, it's not that big a deal!
Did something happen with Hinata?
It's a secret!